Guide to the National Education Association-Special Collections records, 1857-2015 NEA1007.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Projects, 1953-2000; Series 8; 90 Linear Feet
  - News of NEA's Project on the Academically Talented, 1960-1961; series 8 (Box 4345, Folder 4)
  - New Unionism, 1988-2003; Series 8 (Box 4736, Folder 6)
  - New Unionism/Collective Bargaining Project, 1997-1999; Series 8 (Box 4736, Folder 7)
  - Northeast Region State and Local Projects Comprehensive Cooperative Project Agreement [1/2], 2004-2005; Series 8 (Box 4656, Folder 1)
  - Northeast Region State and Local Projects Comprehensive Cooperative Project Agreement [2/2], 2004-2005; Series 8 (Box 4656, Folder 2)
  - Occasional Paper 1 and 2: History of Instructional Technology, ca. 1961; series 8 (Box 4345, Folder 5)
  - Occasional Paper 3: Teaching Machines and Programed Learning 1962: A Survey of the Industry, ca. 1962; series 8 (Box 4345, Folder 6)
  - Occasional Paper 4: Instructional Technology and the Press: A Case Study (Daily Newspaper Treatment of Communication Technology Topics Discussed at the 1961 NEA Convention), ca. 1962; series 8 (Box 4345, Folder 7)
  - Occasional Paper 5: Automatiion in Educational Administration, 1: Vending Machines in Schools and Colleges, ca. 1962; series 8 (Box 4345, Folder 8)
  - Occasional Paper 6: Studies in the Growth of Instructional technology, 1962-1963; series 8 (Box 4345, Folder 9)
  - Occasional Paper 8: The Design of Instructional Equipment: Two Views, ca. 1962; series 4345 (Box 4345, Folder 10)
  - Occasional Paper 9: Revolution in the Textbook Publishing Industry, ca. 1963; series 8 (Box 4345, Folder 11)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Alabama, 1991; Series 8 (Box 2658, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Alabama, 1989-1992; Series 8 (Box 2658, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Alabama-Alabama Education Association, 1993-1998; Series 8 (Box 2658, Folder 6)
    Conditions Governing Access
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Alabama-Community, Junior and Technical Colleges, 1992-1993; Series 8 (Box 2658, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Alabama-Dothan, 1993; Series 8 (Box 2658, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Alabama-Dothan City, 1995; Series 8 (Box 2658, Folder 9)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Alabama-Houston County, 1993-1998; Series 8 (Box 2658, Folder 10)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Alabama-Survey, 1994-1995; Series 8 (Box 2659, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Alaska, 1989-1992; Series 8 (Box 2659, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Arbitrations, 1987; Series 8 (Box 2659, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Area Wage Surveys, 1987-1989; Series 8 (Box 2659, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Arizona [file 1/2], 1987-1992; Series 8 (Box 2659, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Arizona [file 2/2], 1989; Series 8 (Box 2659, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Arizona-Creighton, ca. 1990; Series 8 (Box 2659, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Arizona-Flagstaff, 1999-2000; Series 8 (Box 2659, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Arkansas, 1997-1998; Series 8 (Box 2659, Folder 9)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Arkansas-Camden, Fairview, 1998; Series 8 (Box 2659, Folder 10)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Arkansas-Pulaski County, 1993-1999; Series 8 (Box 2660, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Arthur Young-Job Evaluations Decisions-Band Method, ca. 1990; Series 8 (Box 2660, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Brochure, 1991-1992; Series 8 (Box 2660, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-California-Orange County Public Schools, ca. 1994; Series 8 (Box 2660, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-California-San Diego [file 1/5], 1991; Series 8 (Box 2660, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-California-San Diego [file 2/5], 1990-1991; Series 8 (Box 2660, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-California-San Diego [file 3/5], 1990-1991; Series 8 (Box 2661, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-California-San Diego [file 4/5], 1991; Series 8 (Box 2661, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-California-San Diego [file 5/5], 1989; Series 8 (Box 2661, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-California-San Diego-"Final Report on the NEA Job Evaluation System and Pay Equity Assessment of the San Diego City School District", 1988 June; Series 8 (Box 2661, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-California State Education Association Job Evaluation Guide, 1980; Series 8 (Box 2661, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Canada [file 1/3], 1988-1991; Series 8 (Box 2661, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Canada [file 2/3], 1988; Series 8 (Box 2662, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Canada [file 3/3], 1986-1988; Series 8 (Box 2662, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Canada-Women Administrators (Losing Ground), 1984; Series 8 (Box 2662, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Canadian Teachers Federation, 1984; Series 8 (Box 2662, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Carlsbad (California) Classification System, 1980; Series 8 (Box 2662, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Chapter for Book-"Fair Pay: We're Worth It", 1990; Series 8 (Box 2663, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Charter Schools, 2000 September 7; Series 8 (Box 2663, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Classification/Reclassification Process and Procedures, 1992; Series 8 (Box 2663, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Collective Bargaining, 1991; Series 8 (Box 2663, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Colorado, 1988-1990; Series 8 (Box 2663, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Colorado-Completed Action plan 87-88 (evaluation), 1987-1988; Series 8 (Box 2663, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Colorado-General Information, 1987-1988; Series 8 (Box 2663, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Colorado-General Information, 1988-1989; Series 8 (Box 2663, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Colorado Springs, 1988; Series 8 (Box 2663, Folder 9)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Competing Unions' Pay Equity Work, 1983-1986; Series 8 (Box 2663, Folder 10)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Correspondence, 1997 April; Series 8 (Box 2664, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Contracts/Project Agreements, 1987-1993; Series 8 (Box 2664, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-CW Study/New York State, 1985-1991; Series 8 (Box 2664, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Delaware, 1991-1992; Series 8 (Box 2664, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Denver, 1989-1990; Series 8 (Box 2664, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Denver, 1989-1991; Series 8 (Box 2664, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Denver, 1991; Series 8 (Box 2664, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Denver Action Plan, 1989-1990; Series 8 (Box 2664, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Denver Association of Education Office Personnel, 1990; Series 8 (Box 2664, Folder 9)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Denver-General Information, 1987; Series 8 (Box 2664, Folder 10)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Designing Job Evalution To Meet Comparable Worth Criteria, 1985; Series 8 (Box 2665, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Dunlop Booklet, 1992 January; Series 8 (Box 2665, Folder 2)
    The material in this folder (display sheets) is oversized and has been removed. It is now found in Box 4289, oversize box.
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Durango, 1988-1989; Series 8 (Box 2665, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Education Support Progress and NEA Today (Affiliate Services Public), 1988; Series 8 (Box 2665, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-ESP Organizing Handbook, 1986; Series 8 (Box 2665, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Extra Manual-Originals, 1989-1990; Series 8 (Box 2665, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Ewing & Company-"Understanding Comparable Worth", 1981; Series 8 (Box 2665, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Factor Evaluation System-Job Evaluation System Abridged FES, 1977; Series 8 (Box 2665, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Fair Pay-We're Worth It-Artwork, ca. 1990; Series 8 (Box 2665, Folder 9)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Farmington Final Report, 1988; Series 8 (Box 2665, Folder 10)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Farmington Report Notes [file 1/2], 1990-1991; Series 8 (Box 2665, Folder 11)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Farmington Report Notes [file 2/2], 1988-1990; Series 8 (Box 2665, Folder 12)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Field Reports-M. Johnston, 1989-1990; Series 8 (Box 2666, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-First Steps to Identifying Sex and Race-Based Pay Inequities in a Workplace, 1981-1982; Series 8 (Box 2666, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Florida, 1993-1994; Series 8 (Box 2666, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Florida, 1998; Series 8 (Box 2666, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Florida-Flagler County, 2000; Series 8 (Box 2666, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Florida-Franklin, 1993-1994; Series 8 (Box 2666, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Florida-Marion, 1993-1995; Series 8 (Box 2666, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Florida-Nassau County, 2000; Series 8 (Box 2666, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Florida-Okaloosa [file 1/2], 1994-1996; Series 8 (Box 2666, Folder 9)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Florida-Okaloosa [file 2/2], 1994-1996; Series 8 (Box 2666, Folder 10)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Georgia, 1998; Series 8 (Box 2666, Folder 11)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Georgia-P.E. Projects, 1995-1996; Series 8 (Box 2666, Folder 12)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Harvard Study [file 1/2], 1988-1992; Series 8 (Box 2666, Folder 13)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Harvard Study [file 2/2], 1988-1991; Series 8 (Box 2667, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Harvard University (Dunlop) Contract, 1989-1991; Series 8 (Box 2667, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Hay Job Evaluation System, 1982; Series 8 (Box 2667, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Higher Education Pay Equity, 1989; Series 8 (Box 2667, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Higher Education Salary Equity; Florida, 1988; Series 8 (Box 2667, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-History of Comparable Worth Debate-Newspaper Clippings & Articles '82-'90, 1980-1981; Series 8 (Box 2667, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-History of Comparable Worth Debate-News clippings & Articles '82-'90 [file 2/5], 1982-1990; Series 8 (Box 2668, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-History of Comparable Worth Debate-News Clippings & Articles '82-'90 [file 3/5], 1982-1990; Series 8 (Box 2668, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-History of Comparable Worth Debate-News Clippings & Articles '82-'90 [file 4/5], 1982-1990; Series 8 (Box 2668, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-History of Comparable Worth Debate-News Clippings & Articles '82-'90 [file 5/5], 1982-1990; Series 8 (Box 2668, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Hubbard & Revo-Cohen Final Report-Florida Career Service System, 1986; Series 8 (Box 2668, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Hubbard & Revo-Cohen, Inc., 1992; Series 8 (Box 2668, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Hubbard & Revo-Cohen-Job Evaluation Software System (JESS) and Basic Evaluation Software System (BESS) [file 1/2], 1994-1998; Series 8 (Box 2669, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Hubbard & Revo-Cohen-Job Evaluation Software System (JESS) and Basic Evaluation Software System (BESS) [file 2/2], 1994-1998; Series 8 (Box 2669, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Hubbard & Revo-Cohen-Marketing TESS, 1987; Series 8 (Box 2669, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Illinois-Alton, 2000; Series 8 (Box 2669, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Illinois-List of References, 1999; Series 8 (Box 2669, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Illinois-Statewide ESP Program Discussion, 1987-1991; Series 8 (Box 2669, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Illinois-University of Illinois at Champaign, 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 2669, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Installing TESS, 1989; Series 8 (Box 2669, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Iowa, 1985-1993; Series 8 (Box 2669, Folder 9)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Iowa-Cedar Falls, 1993; Series 8 (Box 2670, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Iowa-Des Moines, 1993 September-October; Series 8 (Box 2670, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Iowa-Northeast Iowa Community College, 1993 April; Series 8 (Box 2670, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Iowa Historical Study [file 1/3], 1987; Series 8 (Box 2670, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Iowa Historical Study [file 2/3], 1984-1985; Series 8 (Box 2670, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Iowa Historical Study [file 3/3], 1984-1985; Series 8 (Box 2670, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Iowa-Report-"Job Evaluation Assessment of Selected Educational Support Personnel Jobs in the Northeast Iowa Community College System", 1995 October; Series 8 (Box 2670, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Iowa State Study [file 1/2], 1984; Series 8 (Box 2670, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Iowa State Study [file 2/2], 1984; Series 8 (Box 2670, Folder 9)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-JESS 3.0, 1990; Series 8 (Box 2671, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-JESS 3.4 (CE's Users Manual), 1991; Series 8 (Box 2671, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-JESS 3.41, 1992; Series 8 (Box 2671, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-JESS 3.42, 1992; Series 8 (Box 2671, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-JESS Traning Materials, 1989-1990; Series 8 (Box 2671, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-JESS version 1.0, ca. 1990; Series 8 (Box 2671, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-JESS Version 3.5 (Regression), ca. 1990; Series 8 (Box 2671, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Job Analysis Questionnaire, ca. 1990; Series 8 (Box 2671, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Job Descriptions, 1991; Series 8 (Box 2671, Folder 9)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Job Evaluation Software System (JESS), 1990 August 22; Series 8 (Box 2671, Folder 10)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Job Evaluation System: Analysis/Comparison-Human Resources vs. NEA Pay Enquiry, 1991; Series 8 (Box 2671, Folder 11)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Job Evaluation Systems, ca. 1990; Series 8 (Box 2671, Folder 12)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Job Rating Manual, ca. 1990; Series 8 (Box 2671, Folder 13)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Kent County, Michigan, 1990-1991; Series 8 (Box 2671, Folder 14)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Las Vegas [file 1/2], 1990; Series 8 (Box 2672, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Las Vegas [file 2/2], 1989-1990; Series 8 (Box 2672, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Lisbon, Maine-Coding, 1989-1990; Series 8 (Box 2672, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Local Project Phases, ca. 1990; Series 8 (Box 2672, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Los Angeles, CA Study, 1981; Series 8 (Box 2672, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Louisiana [file 1/2], 1994-1995; Series 8 (Box 2672, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Louisiana [file 2/2], 1994-1995; Series 8 (Box 2672, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maine [file 1/6], 1984-1988; Series 8 (Box 2673, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maine [file 2/6], 1979-1988; Series 8 (Box 2673, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maine [file 3/6], 1986-1988; Series 8 (Box 2673, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maine [file 4/6], 1986-1987; Series 8 (Box 2673, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maine [file 5/6], 1984; Series 8 (Box 2673, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maine [file 6/6], 1990; Series 8 (Box 2674, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maine (ACSNM)-Job Class System (Proposed), 1986 March; Series 8 (Box 2674, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maine-Lisbon, 1997-1998; Series 8 (Box 2674, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maine-Report-"Lisbon Maine Public Schools Job Classification Assessment Project", 1998 April; Series 8 (Box 2674, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Manual-"Fair Pay-We're Worth It!" [file 1/4], 1990; Series 8 (Box 2674, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Manual-"Fair Pay-We're Worth It!" [file 2/4], 1990; Series 8 (Box 2674, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Manual-"Fair Pay-We're Worth It!" [file 3/4], 1990; Series 8 (Box 2675, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Manual-"Fair Pay-We're Worth It!" [file 4/4], 1990; Series 8 (Box 2675, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maryland [file 1/2], 1990-1992; Series 8 (Box 2675, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maryland [file 2/2], 1990-1992; Series 8 (Box 2675, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maryland-Howard County, 1999-2000; Series 8 (Box 2675, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maryland-"Agreement Between The Classified Employees Assoc. of St. Mary's County and The Board of Education of St. Mary's County", 1996 July 1-1998 June 30; Series 8 (Box 2675, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maryland-Prince George's County, 1998-2000; Series 8 (Box 2675, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maryland-St. Mary's County, 1987-1997; Series 8 (Box 2676, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maryland-Washington County, 1998-1999; Series 8 (Box 2676, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maryland-Washington County Educational Classified Employees Association, 1997-1998; Series 8 (Box 2676, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maryland-Wicomico County, 2000; Series 8 (Box 2676, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Maryland-Worcester, 1997; Series 8 (Box 2676, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Massachusetts-Pay Equity Study [file 1/2], 1986; Series 8 (Box 2676, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Massachusetts-Pay Equity Study [file 2/2], 1986; Series 8 (Box 2676, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Mesa, 1988-1989; Series 8 (Box 2676, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Michigan-East Grand Rapids [file 1/3], 1995-1998; Series 8 (Box 2676, Folder 9)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Michigan-East Grand Rapids [file 2/3], 1995-1998; Series 8 (Box 2676, Folder 10)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Michigan-East Grand Rapids [file 3/3], 1995-1998; Series 8 (Box 2677, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Michigan-State Program, 1988-1990; Series 8 (Box 2677, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Minnesota, 1980-1989; Series 8 (Box 2677, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Minnesota-Job Matching, 1984-1990; Series 8 (Box 2677, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Miscellaneous, 1994; Series 8 (Box 2677, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Miscellaneous-California State Education Association Projects, 1976-1978; Series 8 (Box 2677, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Mississippi, 1998 October; Series 8 (Box 2677, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Montana, 1991-1993; Series 8 (Box 2677, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Montana-Fact-Finding Information, 1988 March 22; Series 8 (Box 2678, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-National Consultant List Job Class/Pay Equity, 1989; Series 8 (Box 2678, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-National Committee on Pay Equity [file 1/2], 1987; Series 8 (Box 2678, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-National Committee on Pay Equity [file 2/2], 1989-1990; Series 8 (Box 2678, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-NCPE Annual Report and Annual Meeting Notes, 1991; Series 8 (Box 2678, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-NCPE Annual Membership Meeting, 1992 November 23; Series 8 (Box 2678, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-NCPE: Information Materials/reports/News notes [file 1/2], 1987-1990; Series 8 (Box 2679, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-NCPE: Information Materials/Reports/News notes [file 2/2], 1989-1990; Series 8 (Box 2679, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-NCPE-US-Canada Dialogue, 1992 November 23; Series 8 (Box 2679, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-NEA Affiliate Services Compensation Program, 1988; Series 8 (Box 2679, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-NEA Job Analysis Questionnaire, 1988-1990; Series 8 (Box 2679, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-NEA Job Analysis Questionnaire, ca. 1990; Series 8 (Box 2679, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-NEA Job Analysis Questionnaire [file 1/2], ca. 1990; Series 8 (Box 2679, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-NEA Job Analysis Questionnaire [file 2/2], ca. 1990; Series 8 (Box 2679, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-NEA Job Evaluation System-Copyright Information [file 1/2], 1990-1991; Series 8 (Box 2680, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-NEA Job Evaluation System-Copyright Information [file 2/2], 1990-1991; Series 8 (Box 2680, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-NEA Job Analysis Questionnaire Draft (Boston Cadre), 1990 September; Series 8 (Box 2680, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-NEA Job Analysis Questionnaire-Modified Version, 1989; Series 8 (Box 2680, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-NEA Research Pay Equity Work, 1987-1988; Series 8 (Box 2680, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Nevada-Clark County, 1992-1993; Series 8 (Box 2680, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Nevada-Las Vegas, 1991; Series 8 (Box 2680, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Nevada-Las Vegas, 1991 March; Series 8 (Box 2680, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-New Hampshire [file 1/2], 1991-1997; Series 8 (Box 2681, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-New Hampshire [file 2/2], 1991-1997; Series 8 (Box 2681, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-New York, 1992-1994; Series 8 (Box 2681, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-New York [file 1/2], 1995; Series 8 (Box 2681, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-New York [file 2/2], 1995; Series 8 (Box 2681, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-NY State Pay Equity Study, ca. 1990; Series 8 (Box 2682, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-News Articles, 1980-1989; Series 8 (Box 2682, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-OESPA, ca. 1990; Series 8 (Box 2682, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Ohio-Dublin [file 1/3], 1998; Series 8 (Box 2682, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Ohio-Dublin [file 2/3], 1997-1998; Series 8 (Box 2682, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Ohio-Dublin [file 3/3], 1997; Series 8 (Box 2682, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Ohio Education Association, 1987-1991; Series 8 (Box 2682, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Ohio-Worthington [file 1/2], 1998; Series 8 (Box 2682, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Ohio-Worthington [file 2/2], 1998; Series 8 (Box 2682, Folder 9)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Oklahoma, 1988; Series 8 (Box 2682, Folder 10)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Oklahoma-Federal Challenge, 1988; Series 8 (Box 2683, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Oklahoma-Other Sites, 1988; Series 8 (Box 2683, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Optional Scan Survey, 1993; Series 8 (Box 2683, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Optional Scan Survey Project, 1991; Series 8 (Box 2683, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Oregon, 1991-1993; Series 8 (Box 2683, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Oregon-ESP Employee Rights Manual, 1986-1987; Series 8 (Box 2683, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Oregon-Legal Rights Conference, 1991 May 18-19; Series 8 (Box 2683, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Oregon-Oregon Education Assoc. Agreement, 1986-1989; Series 8 (Box 2683, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Oregon-Salem, 1989-1991; Series 8 (Box 2683, Folder 9)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Oregon-Salem-Keizer [file 1/4], 1988-1991; Series 8 (Box 2684, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Oregon-Salem-Keizer [file 2/4], 1988-1991; Series 8 (Box 2684, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Oregon-Salem-Keizer [file 3/4], 1988-1991; Series 8 (Box 2684, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Oregon-Salem-Keizer [file 4/4], 1988-1991; Series 8 (Box 2684, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Organizing for Membership Growth, ca. 1990; Series 8 (Box 2684, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Organizing Seminar, 1991; Series 8 (Box 2684, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Originals, 1990; Series 8 (Box 2684, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Paraprofessionals, The Role of, 1989; Series 8 (Box 2685, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Packet-"Human and Civil Rights: Working Toward Excellence and Equity", ca. 1990; Series 8 (Box 2685, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Pay Equity & Public Employees Minnesota Report, 1981; Series 8 (Box 2685, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Pennsylvania, 1983-1992; Series 8 (Box 2685, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Pennsylvania, 1992-1996; Series 8 (Box 2685, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Pennsylvania-Beaver County Community College [file 1/2], 1995-1996; Series 8 (Box 2685, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Pennsylvania-Beaver County Community College [file 2/2], 1995-1996; Series 8 (Box 2685, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Personnel Resources (Projects), ca. 1990; Series 8 (Box 2685, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Phil Zollo, 1992-1993; Series 8 (Box 2685, Folder 9)
    Zollo, Felix J., Jr.
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Phil Zollo Communications, 1999-2000; Series 8 (Box 2686, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity and Jobs-Phoenix, 1989; Series 8 (Box 2686, Folder 2)